Guide to the James Buell Munn Collection 1873-1980 MC 2 MC.2
New York University Archives
- Series I: Family
  - Subseries C: Martha Buell Plum Munn
    - Legal Papers Will and Codicil; handwritten notes on envelope addressed to John M. Recht (Grandson), no author., 1915-1916, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries D: Other Family
    - Biographical Data Aristine Pixley Munn (JBM's sister) birth certificate; letter of congratulations from Rev.,George Alexander., 1887 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence References to the Munn Farm and medical assistance pro­ vided to Munn's students. Correspondents include JBM's cousins Fannie Munn Field and John Munn Hanford, M.D., and letter from an unidentified nephew., 1923-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings Obituaries of Fannie Munn Field (not the same person who lived on the Munn Farm during the 1920'x; 1873); Martha Buell Plum (JBM's grandmother; 1874); Aristine Pixley Munn Recht (April, 1952); Charles Recht (husband of Aristine; July 1965)., 1873-1874, 1952, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Obituary: James Buell, 1881 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Series II: James Buell Munn
  - Subseries A: Biographical Data
    - Certificate of Baptism Includes certificate and letter of congratulations from Rev. George Alexander., 1891 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Sketch Bibliography listed in National Union Catalog Imprints; Sketch in Who's Who in America., 1956, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Minute, 1968
  - Subseries B: Harvard University
    - Sub-subseries 1: Student Years at Harvard, 1909-1912
      - Correspondence Includes decision to enter teaching profession and demonstrates JBM's contact with Harvard since his graduation­ in 1912. Correspondents include Arthur Beane, Paul H. Buck, Erwin N. Griswold, John Livingston Jones, Delmar Leighton, A. Lawrence, Harlow Shapley, Randall Thompson, Winthrop W. Wade., 1913-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Student Records JBM's report card (1909-1910 academic year); questionnaire, Class of 1912., 1909-1912 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Tributes Includes letters and poetry from former Harvard students; donations to Harvard Library's Milton Collection; press release and obituary., 1936-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Writings review by JBM in Harvard Divinity Bulletin: Herman Melville: The Tragedy of Mind by William Ellery Sedgwick., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries 2:Teaching Years at Harvard, 1932-1957
      - Correspondence: Maud M. Arrosell, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Joe & Addie Davey, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence: Delmar Leighton, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence: A.P., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: John M. Recht, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence: Dan Tuite, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - History of A Gray Lowery Day, Painting by George Inness, 1976
      - Walter Channing Cabot Fellow Award, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Harvard Library Bulletin, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Subseries C: New York University
    - General Includes Certificate of Honorary Membership, Menorah Society; list of appointments and salary, Washington Square College (1920-1932); references and picture in "New York University Notebook," May, 1963 (50th anniversary of Washington Square College issue)., 1932, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Administrative/Teaching Duties - Correspondence (folder, 1917-1926 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Administrative/Teaching Duties - Correspondence (folder 2) Folders contain material relating to Biology Department administrative issue; English Department course listings, 1926-27, 1927-28;.development of a liberal arts music course, 1932; and general correspondence re Summer School courses taught by JBM, general teaching and administrative duties. A.A. Beaumont, A.L. Bouton, Elmer E. Brown, James Buchman, Miguel de Capriles, Henry J. Fry, Jacob D. Goldstein, Ruth B. Howland, William Ford Manley, Alfred L. Mannhardt, Douglas A. Marsland, John Musser, Richard H. Bitter, John Roscoe Turner, Harold 0. Voorhis, Homer A. Watt. Correspondents upon resignation in 1932 (beyond above list) include Ralph Beals, Oscar Cargill, Ralph H. Cheney, Frank E. Crawford, Lloyd E. Dewey, Benjamin T. Fairchild, Fred I. Kent, Fiske Kimball, LeRoy E. Kimball, David Sarnofft Percy S. Strauss, 1926-1932 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Administrative/Teaching Duties - Reports/Statistical-Data Includes reports detailing Washington Square College student registration, age, religious affiliation-.-employment; Annual Report of Dean of Washington Square College to the Chancellor., 1919-1929 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence to Social Register Association, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Donations to New York University - Correspondence Contains material relevant to donations from JBM and his family re improvements in Main Building, books for the Correspondents include LeRoy E. Kimball, R.V.D. Magoffin, H.O. Voorhis., 1923-1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Donations to New York University - Receipts, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Degree Memorabilia, includes tickets, commencement booklet., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: H. Thomas Austern, 1925-1953, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: B - Correspondents include Jacob Bacals, Louis Baron, Bernard Barron, Harry Baum, Milton J. Billard, Samuel Bloustein (father of Francis Bloustein), Charles Bloom, George A. Borchard, Frank Brieff, Benjamin B. Butner., 1923-1953, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: C - Correspondents include Kenneth Carroad, Yale Julius Carroad, William Charvat, Ralph Cirillo, Harold B. Clemenko, Norman W. Cohen, Samuel Cohen, Jennie Crosby (mother of Lawrence Crosby)., ca.1920-1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Eugene Davidson -, 1925-1926 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Miguel A. de Capriles -, 1925-1962 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: E - Correspondents include Harry Epstein, Lee Epstein, Julius Evans, 1926, 1945-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: F - Correspondents inclu a Oscar H. Fidell, Jacob Fisher, Sylvia K. Fishman (wife of Meyer Fishman, both knew Munn)., 1923, 1945-1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: G - Includes correspondence from Munn. Correspondents include Morris Gelfand, Max Goldstone, Bernard Goodman., 1925-1926, 1945-1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Jacob Goldstein -, 1923, 1950-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: George R. Gomperts - Includes correspondence from Munn., 1925-1926, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Fred Hess -, 1923-1926 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: H - Correspondents include Jerrold Holmes, Richard Hyman., 1920-1926 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: I-J - Correspondents include Benjamin Jack, Nathaniel Janes, Irving Jurow., 1920-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Isidore S. Immerman -, 1926-1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Murray Israel - (1920's). Includes article on arteriosclerosis by M. Israel published by the Vascular Research Foundation, 1949; Annual Review, of Vascular Research Foundation memorial issue dedicated to JBM, 1967-68; correspondence from Mrs. Israel., 1949-1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Nathaniel Jackson -, 1923-1925 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: K-L - Includes correspondence from Munn. Correspondents include Jacob Keppler, A1 Klotz, Harry Knodue, Charles Krevisky, Victor Lehman, Hyman Lehon, Morris B. Lichtenstein, Terry Mangin Logan, Robert Lustgarten, 1924-1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Manfred B. Lee (one-half of "Ellery Queen") Includes correspondence from Munn and letter from Mrs. Lee to Mrs. Munn (1974)., 1926-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: M-N - Correspondents include James Mandel, Lester Moledezkyp Francis Nance., 1925-1974 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Charles Norman - Correspondence, includes poetry - April, 1925-May, 1943 Correspondence, includes poetry - March, 1944-Aug, 1966; n.d. Poetry - n.d., undated, 1925-1966 (Box 4, Folder 27-29)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: P - Includes correspondence from Munn,. Correspondents include James C. Paradise, Louis Pincus, Meyer Poses, Morris Pottish., 1925-1956 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Morris Ploscowe - Includes correspondence from Munn., ca.1920-1953 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: R - Correspondents include Adolph Raboff, Jacob Rabkin, John C. Roberts, David H. Ross., 1922-1953 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Charles Rosenblum - Includes correspondence from Munn., 1924-1953 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: S - Includes correspondence from Munn. Correspondents include Phillip B. Sahn, Lester Samelson, George Saslow, Harry Schreck, Howard Schwarzel, Harold R. Shapiro, Victor Shapiro, Harry W. Shulsky (Starr), Abraham Smith, Joseph Smolack., ca.1920-1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: U-V-W - Includes-correspondence-from Munn* Correspondents include Samson Ullman, Jr., Henry Volksening, Herman J. Wechsler, Benjamin Weinstein, Benjamin Wiesel., 1926-1949 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence with: Z - Includes correspondence from Munn. Correspondents include Louis Zeidberg, Benjamin Ziegler, Emmanuel Ziegler., ca.1920-1958 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Munn Students - Correspondence Relating to Includes academic support and medical assistance provides by JBM. Correspondents include J.W. Barlow, Dugald E.S. Brown, Morton C. Campbell, Roscoe Pound, Alfred R. Starr., 1923-1929 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Munn Students - Schedule A Fund - Memoranda Includes lists of students who received financial aid from JBM through the account "Schedule A", and Washington Square College Loan Fund listings, 1924-1925. Correspondents include LeRoy E. Kimball., 1923-1930 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Munn Students - Schedule A Fund - Receipts, 1923-1930 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Munn Students - Receipts (not Schedule A Fund) Includes medical bills; bills for clothing, books; transfer of funds., 1928-1930 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Munn Students - Printed Material Includes articles about: Jacob D. Goldstein - University of Rochester newsletter, n. d. Charles Norman - The Villager, Jan. 29, 1948 George Wald - New York University Alumni News, Nov., 1967, 1948-1967 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence with Charles H. Webster, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence with Leon Pressman, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Music Appreciation Course - Folders 42-43 contain suggested curriculum (no author); bibliographies and catalogs of music, records, and musical equipment; Carnegie Corporation, "Analysis of Grants in the Field of Music during the Period October 1, 1921- April 1, 1931." Folder 44 contains duplicates of materials in folders 42 and 43., 1930-1934 (Box 5, Folder 42-44)
    - Writings at Washington Square College "The Washington Square College," drafted by JBM for Dean Roscoe Turner. Is a brief history of Washington Square College, 1915-1925 and includes Munn's analysis of Washington Square College as an urban college and the need for good pre-professional/liberal arts training. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Washington Square College Bulletin Notations by JBM, pp. 11-12., 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Post-Resignation - Correspondence (folder 1), 1932-1948 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Post-Resignation - Correspondence (folder 2) Folders contain material relating to Harvard appointment in 1932; evaluation of JBM by H.A. Watt in 1933; New York University Honorary Degree, June, 1945; biography of Thomas Wolfe (unfinished?) by H.A. Watt and research for collec­tion of Wolfe letters, 1946-1950; recommendations for open positions at New York University. Correspondents include Alexander Baltzly, A.A. Beaumont, Elmer E. Brown, Oscar Cargill, Bruce Carpenter, Henry A. Charipper, Harry Woodburn Chase, Walter W.S. Cook, Fred Johnson, James Mandell Douglas A. Marsland, Frank H. McClosky, Nelson McCombs, Thomas Clark Pollock, Harold 0. Voorhis, Mrs. H.A. Watt, Effie Watt (daughter) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Subseries D: Munn Farm
    - Correspondence Correspondence with employees and a contractor., 1925-1926 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Visitors' Registers - "J.B.'s Prize Pigs", ca.1920 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Visitors' Registers - "Register" The two registers contain names and addresses of students who spent summers at the Munn Farm. There are also casual notations., 1924-1930 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cattle Letter from JBM (September 1926) re transfer of cattle from estate of Fannie Munn Field. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Subseries E: Organizations (cont'd.)
    - First Presbyterian Church of New York City - Correspondence Includes references to JBM's ordination as an elder. Correspondents include the Rev. George Alexander., 1891-1932 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - First Presbyterian Church of New York City - George Alexander Includes eulogy, no author; dedication booklet - Alexander Memorial Chapel; notations by JBM (for memorial plaque?)., 1930-1938 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Organizations - Correspondents Includes membership correspondence; School Board No. 8 minutes and correspondence; correspondence re acquisition by Harvard Club of NYC of Henry James' music Library and financial support for graduates of New York City high schools at Harvard University; correspondence re Henry Sloan Coffin assuming presidency of Oratorio Society. Organizations include: American Museum of Natural History American Officers of the Great War Club of Odd Volumes Harvard Club of New York City Helfenstein Chorister Institute, Inc. Local School Board No. 8 (NYC) Medieval Academy of America National Educational Association Oratorio Society of New York Society of Mayflower Descendants: Correspondents include Henry Sloan Coffin, Henry James (letter of November 26, 1926)., 1919-1928 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subseries F: Appointment Books
    - Appointment Books (folder 1), 1921-1926 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Books (folder 2) Folders include JBM's 1921. academic schedule; appointments with students and faculty; e names and addresses of Munn Students., 1927-1930 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Writings
    - As a Child n.d. Folder contains two pieces: scribbles, and a short, unaddressed thank-you note. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks - Black (folder 1), 1910-1915 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Notebooks - Green (folder 2) Notebooks contain JBM's introspective memoirs about his Harvard student and post-student years; army experiences; decision to remain in New York City in 1919; early reaction to students of Washington Square College; poetry, short story. (xerox copies - originals in Harvard University Archives, 1913-1921 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Handwritten Notes Includes eulogy (read by JBM?) at his mother's grave; calendar note entered day John Pixley Munn died., 1926-1931 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Handwritten Notes Two notes written by JBM found by Mrs. Munn in his desk (Aug.) and wallet (Sept,) With envelopes containing Mrs. Munns notations., undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Subseries H: Legal Papers
    - Legal Papers Includes legacy to JBM under will of his mother, Martha Buell Plum Munn: correspondence, list of share, charts of financial data; contract with Scott Foresman & Company re Ideas & Forms in English and American Literature written with Homer A. Watt; miscellaneous items: notarial certi­ficate of protest re unpaid check; affidavit re medical discharge of private in JBM's army unit. :­, 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries I: Newspaper Clippings
    - Newspaper Clippings Includes JBM's views on Washington Square College as an urban college; appointment to Harvard in 1932; marriage to Ruth Crosby Hanford Munn; appointment as Chairman of Harvard English Department in 1934; gift to Gates Presbyterian Church in 1935; New York University Honorary Degree in 1945; announcement of James Buell Munn Scholarship Fund, New York University in 1963; obituaries, 1967, 1928-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subseries J: Ruth Crosby Hanford Munn
    - General Correspondence Correspondents include Alexander Baltzly, Bruce Carpenter Jacob D. Goldstein, JBM., 1942-1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - J.B. Munn Library/Gift of Mrs. Munn to Boston Public Library­ Correspondence Correspondents include Walter Grossman, Philip J. McNiff, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - J.B. Munn Library/Gift of Mrs. Munn to Boston Public Library - Newspaper Clippings Descriptive material about the Boston Public Library, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Series III: The James Buell Munn Scholarship Fund
  - Correspondence: Includes correspondence regarding establishment and funding of the Scholarship Fund; 1965 list of alumni pledges and payments. Correspondents include Louis Baron, A.A. Beaumont, William E. Buckler, Miguel A. de Capriles, Jacob D. Goldstein, James M. Hester, Irving H. Jurow, Ruth C.H. Munn*, 1962-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Lists: Includes lists of former Munn Students sent by Mrs. Munn to Jacob Do Goldstein., 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, Steering Committee, Descriptive Material: Minutes of steering committee meetings; list of pledges; Treasurer's Report; press release announcing JBM Scholar­ship Fund; description written for circular letter; "A Report on the First Five Years of the James B. Munn Scholarship Fund,", 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Memoirs: Contributors include A.A. Beaumont, Irwin D. Davidson, Erwin N. Griswold, Hyman Lehon, Sidney Hook., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous
  - Inventories: Inventories of materials in the James Buell Munn Estate Collection brought to the New York University Archives by Jacob D. Goldstein., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Series V: Photographs/Artifact
  - Subseries A: James Buell Munn
    - As a young boy, on Munn Farm, as a young man, sophomore year at Harvard University. See also: oversized folder--301st Officers' Corps, 1918; Munn Farm, folders #1 and 2., 1905-1925 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - James Buell Munn, 1900-1930 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Munn Family.
    - Group Photographs: Includes Mrs. Elias Plum; John P. Munn; Mrs, John P. Aunn; JBM and Aristine P. Munn; Fannie hunn Field; Harold Pixley; Munn-Pixley. See also: oversized folder: JBM; Aristine P. Munn; John P. Munn., 1887-1925 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Aristine Pixley Munn (Mrs. Edwin G. Munn) n.d.; in middle age., undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - John Pixley Munn n.d. As a young boy; a young man; in old age. See also: oversized folder -, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Martha Buell Plum Munn (Mrs. John P. Munn) n. d. As a young woman. See also: oversized folder, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Aristine Pixley Munn 1903; n.d. As a young woman. See also: oversized folder--n.d.; as a young woman. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Fannie Munn Field At the Munn Farm. See also: Munn Farm, folder #1., 1924-1925 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Aristine Pixley Munn and James Buell Munn, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Group Photographs, 1890s-1900s (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - John Pixley Munn (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Martha Buell Plum Munn, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Aristine Pixley Munn (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Fannie Munn Field at the Farm, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: Munn Family Associates.
    - Reverend George Alexander, n.d. Helen Gould, n.d. (with two unidentified Gould cousins, with the Munn family) Jay Gould, n.d. Higgins and Hughs families, n.d. (with Munn family) Dr. and Mrs. Leonard Putzel (Munn family doctor), nod. (with Munn family and Dr. Charles Recht, Aristine P. Munn's husband). Maude Russell (Dr. John P. Munn and Mrs. Munn's nurse), 1925-1927 at the Munn Farm. Russell Sage, n.d. Mr. and Mrs. H. Robinson Shipherd, 1912 (with Munn Family), 1912-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries D: New York University - Associates
    - Chancellor Henry M. MacCracken family, n.d. (with Munn family on the University Heights campus) Homer A. Watt, 1947. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Munn Students - at the Munn Farm
    - Includes: Louis Baron, Benjamin Bezarsky, Francis Bloustein, William Charvot, Ralph Cirillo, Harold B. Clemenko, Norman Cohen, Miguel de Capriles, Harry Epstein,, Julius Evans, Lester Feinstein, Jacob D. Goldstein, Max Goldstone, George Compertz, Bernard Goodman, Milton Herman, Frank Hess, Ben W. Holler, Murray Israel, Nathaniel H. Jackson, Irving H. Jurow, Charles Krevisky, 1924-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Otto Losa, Lester Morely (Maledezky), Francis Nance, Lester Platt, Meyer Poses, Morris Pottish, Jacob Rabkin, Charles Rosenblum, Lester Samuelson, Victor Shapiro, Harry Shulsky (Starr), Max Som (Somme), Louis Zeidberg, Benjamin Zeigler., 1924-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Includes: Louis Baron, Benjamin Bezarsky, Francis Bloustein, Morris Gelfand, Murray Israel, Nathaniel H. Jackson, Otto Los a., Lester Morley (Maledezky), Harry Shulsky (Starr), Max Som (Somme), 1928 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Identification of photographs of the Munn Students at the Munn Farm by Dr. Jacob D. Goldstein. Munn Farm, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Munn Students at Munn Farm, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: Munn Farm
    - Includes: scenes of the farm and photographs of farm employees (Mr. and Mrs. Albert Verhage, rielen Verhage). There are photographs of the farm's manage, Simon West, and other unidentified farm employees in several of the group photographs of the Munn Students (Subseries El, folder l)., 1924-1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Munn Farm
  - Subseries G: Artifact/Mann Farm
    - Silver cup given by Munn Students ("Prize Figs") to Fannie Munn Field, 1924. Daguerreotypes: 1. Martha Maria Buell Plum (Mrs. Elias Plum) with Martha Buell Plum Munn (Mrs. John T. Munn) as a small girl; n.d. 2. Martha Buell Plum Munn as a young woman; n.d. 3. John P. Munn as a young boy; n.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Research Material
  - Research Binder (1of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Research Binder (2 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Physiologia Epicuro-Gassendo-Charltoniana, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    General Note
    The origin of these photocopies is unknown.
- Addendum - Series I: Acquisition
  - Acquisition of Estate Collection/Munn Memorial Collection - Correspondence Includes correspondence, chronology describing the acquisition of the Munn Papers; Memorandum, c. Feb., 1977 by Jacob D. Goldstein detailing the history of the Estate Collection; "Major Achievements in the Archives Since Last Meeting of the Council," by Bayrd Still. Correspondents include Jacob D. Goldstein, Harley P. Holden, Hyman Lehon, Clifford H. Shipton, Bayrd Still. See also: Professor Still files for post-1978 correspondence., 1952-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Contributions to Memorial Fund - Correspondence Material re receipt of funding needed to arrange the Estate Collection and develop the Memorial Collection. Correspondents include H. Thomas Austern, Jacob D. Goldstein, Jacob Rabkin, Bayrd Still., undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Lists Includes lists of former students who contributed to fund for Mrs. Yerhage (Munn farm employee); former students who con­ tributed to Munn Scholarship Fund; students identified by B. Parnes as correspondents of Munn., undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Returned Letters Letters returned per "addressee Unknown.", undated (Box 10, Folder 4)